[
{ "ID":20000, "name":"鸾凤火羽", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10001_charge_back", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10001_charge_front", "selfAniTime":2.5, "selfDelay":0.5, "targetAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10001_target_back", "targetAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10001_target_back", "targetAniTime":4, "targetDelay":2.5, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":1.5, "hitDelay":1.5, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20001, "name":"花容月貌", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10002_charge", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10002_charge", "selfAniTime":2.5, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":1, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20002, "name":"洛水巨浪", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10003_charge", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10003_charge", "selfAniTime":2.5, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10003_target_back", "targetAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10003_target_front", "targetAniTime":1.5, "targetDelay":1.5, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10003_hit", "hitAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10003_hit", "hitAniTime":0.8, "hitDelay":1.9, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20003, "name":"寒霜降世", "selfAni_Back":"Effect/SkillEffect/10004_charge", "selfAni_Front":"Effect/SkillEffect/10004_charge", "selfAniTime":2.6, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"Effect/SkillEffect/10004_target", "targetAni_Front":"Effect/SkillEffect/10004_target", "targetAniTime":2, "targetDelay":1.56, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20004, "name":"方天画戟", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10005_Charge", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10005_Charge", "selfAniTime":1.7, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10005_target_back", "targetAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10005_target_front", "targetAniTime":1.6, "targetDelay":1.5, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10005_hit", "hitAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10005_hit", "hitAniTime":0.8, "hitDelay":1.6, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20005, "name":"龙牙突刺", "selfAni_Back":"Effect/SkillEffect/10006_charge_back", "selfAni_Front":"Effect/SkillEffect/10006_charge_front", "selfAniTime":2.6, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"Effect/SkillEffect/10006_target", "targetAni_Front":"Effect/SkillEffect/10006_target", "targetAniTime":2, "targetDelay":1.47, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20006, "name":"青龙狂斩", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10007_Charge", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10007_Charge", "selfAniTime":1.4, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10007_target_back", "targetAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10007_target_front", "targetAniTime":2.5, "targetDelay":1.4, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10007_hit", "hitAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10007_hit", "hitAniTime":1, "hitDelay":1.5, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20007, "name":"破军咆哮", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10008_Charge_back", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10008_Charge_front", "selfAniTime":2.5, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10008_target_back", "targetAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10008_target_front", "targetAniTime":4, "targetDelay":1.4, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20008, "name":"仁德之治", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10009_Charge", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10009_Charge", "selfAniTime":2.2, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10009_target", "targetAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10009_target", "targetAniTime":1.7, "targetDelay":1.5, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20009, "name":"君王权谋", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10010_Charge", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10010_Charge", "selfAniTime":0.9, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"WarEffect/9005_back", "targetAni_Front":"WarEffect/9005_front", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":1.5, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10010_hit", "hitAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10010_hit", "hitAniTime":1, "hitDelay":1.5, "hitCycle":0.3 },
{ "ID":20010, "name":"精雕怒射", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10011_Charge_back", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10011_Charge_front", "selfAniTime":2.8, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":0, "flyAni":"FX/skillEffect/10011_fly", "flyType":2, "flySpd":24, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":1.2, "hitAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10011_hit", "hitAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10011_hit", "hitAniTime":1, "hitDelay":1.2, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20011, "name":"乱世枭雄", "selfAni_Back":"Effect/SkillEffect/10012_charge", "selfAni_Front":"Effect/SkillEffect/10012_charge", "selfAniTime":2.5, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"Effect/SkillEffect/10012_target", "targetAni_Front":"Effect/SkillEffect/10012_target", "targetAniTime":2.5, "targetDelay":1.35, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20012, "name":"江水天寒", "selfAni_Back":"Effect/SkillEffect/10013_charge", "selfAni_Front":"Effect/SkillEffect/10013_charge", "selfAniTime":2.5, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":0, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20013, "name":"三军箭雨", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10014_Charge_back", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10014_Charge_front", "selfAniTime":1.8, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10014_target_back", "targetAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10014_target_front", "targetAniTime":2.5, "targetDelay":1.5, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20014, "name":"虎狼之师", "selfAni_Back":"Effect/SkillEffect/10015_Charge_back", "selfAni_Front":"Effect/SkillEffect/10015_Charge_front", "selfAniTime":2, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":0, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20015, "name":"奇门遁甲", "selfAni_Back":"Effect/SkillEffect/10016_Charge_back", "selfAni_Front":"Effect/SkillEffect/10016_Charge_front", "selfAniTime":2.4, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":0, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"Effect/SkillEffect/10016_hit", "hitAni_Front":"Effect/SkillEffect/10016_hit", "hitAniTime":1.5, "hitDelay":1.5, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20016, "name":"万雷惊神", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10017_Charge_back", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10017_Charge_front", "selfAniTime":2.2, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10017_target", "targetAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10017_target", "targetAniTime":3, "targetDelay":1.5, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10017_hit", "hitAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10017_hit", "hitAniTime":1, "hitDelay":1.4, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20017, "name":"破釜沉舟", "selfAni_Back":"Effect/SkillEffect/10018_Charge", "selfAni_Front":"Effect/SkillEffect/10018_Charge", "selfAniTime":2, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":1.5, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20018, "name":"蛮锤重击", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10019_Charge", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10019_Charge", "selfAniTime":2, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10019_target_back", "targetAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10019_target_front", "targetAniTime":1.6, "targetDelay":1.4, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20019, "name":"火烧连营", "selfAni_Back":"Effect/SkillEffect/10020_Charge_back", "selfAni_Front":"Effect/SkillEffect/10020_Charge_front", "selfAniTime":2, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"Effect/SkillEffect/10020_target", "targetAni_Front":"Effect/SkillEffect/10020_target", "targetAniTime":2.5, "targetDelay":1.6, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20020, "name":"山崩地裂", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10021_Charge_back", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10021_Charge_front", "selfAniTime":3, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10021_target_back", "targetAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10021_target_front", "targetAniTime":2.5, "targetDelay":1.5, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20021, "name":"将魂庇佑", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10022_Charge", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10022_Charge", "selfAniTime":2.5, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":0, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20022, "name":"秘计攻心", "selfAni_Back":"Effect/SkillEffect/10023_Charge_back", "selfAni_Front":"Effect/SkillEffect/10023_Charge_front", "selfAniTime":2.4, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"WarEffect/9029", "targetAni_Front":"WarEffect/9029", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":1.4, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"Effect/SkillEffect/10023_hit", "hitAni_Front":"Effect/SkillEffect/10023_hit", "hitAniTime":1.5, "hitDelay":1.2, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20023, "name":"龙啸于渊", "selfAni_Back":"WarEffect/9030_100_back", "selfAni_Front":"WarEffect/9030_100_front", "selfAniTime":0, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":1.2, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20024, "name":"天赐甘露", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10025_charge_back", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10025_charge_front", "selfAniTime":3.3, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10025_target", "targetAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10025_target", "targetAniTime":1.5, "targetDelay":1.5, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10025_hit", "hitAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10025_hit", "hitAniTime":2, "hitDelay":1.5, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20025, "name":"群星坠落", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10026_charge", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10026_charge", "selfAniTime":1.6, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10026_target_back", "targetAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10026_target_back", "targetAniTime":2, "targetDelay":1.5, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20026, "name":"神枪百炼", "selfAni_Back":"WarEffect/9031_100_back", "selfAni_Front":"WarEffect/9031_100_front", "selfAniTime":0, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"WarEffect/9031_front", "targetAni_Front":"WarEffect/9031_back", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":1.5, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20027, "name":"冥魂暗箭", "selfAni_Back":"WarEffect/9006_100_back", "selfAni_Front":"WarEffect/9006_100_front", "selfAniTime":0, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":1.2, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20028, "name":"御奔突袭", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10029_charge_back", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10029_charge_front", "selfAniTime":2.5, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10029_target_back", "targetAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10029_target_front", "targetAniTime":2.5, "targetDelay":1.5, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10029_hit", "hitAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10029_hit", "hitAniTime":1.5, "hitDelay":2.5, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20029, "name":"凤雏降龙", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10030_Charge_back", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10030_Charge_front", "selfAniTime":2.8, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":0, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20030, "name":"冰封万里", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10031_Charge", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10031_Charge", "selfAniTime":2.5, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10031_target_back", "targetAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10031_target_front", "targetAniTime":2, "targetDelay":2, "flyAni":"FX/skillEffect/10031_fly", "flyType":1, "flySpd":24, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":1.5, "hitAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10031_hit", "hitAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10031_hit", "hitAniTime":2, "hitDelay":2, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20031, "name":"踏月连击", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10032_Charge_back", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10032_Charge_front", "selfAniTime":1.8, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10032_target_back", "targetAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10032_target_front", "targetAniTime":1.7, "targetDelay":1.5, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20032, "name":"刀光剑影", "selfAni_Back":"Effect/SkillEffect/10033_Charge_back", "selfAni_Front":"Effect/SkillEffect/10033_Charge_front", "selfAniTime":2.3, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":1.5, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"Effect/SkillEffect/10033_hit", "hitAni_Front":"Effect/SkillEffect/10033_hit", "hitAniTime":1.5, "hitDelay":1.45, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20033, "name":"", "selfAni_Back":"", "selfAni_Front":"", "selfAniTime":0, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":0, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20034, "name":"王佐秘技", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10035_Charge_back", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10035_Charge_front", "selfAniTime":3, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10035_target", "targetAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10035_target", "targetAniTime":2.5, "targetDelay":1.6, "flyAni":"FX/skillEffect/10035_fly", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20035, "name":"青羽飞扬", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10036_Charge_back", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10036_Charge_front", "selfAniTime":2.5, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10036_target_back", "targetAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10036_target_front", "targetAniTime":1.5, "targetDelay":1.5, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20036, "name":"", "selfAni_Back":"", "selfAni_Front":"", "selfAniTime":0, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":0, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20037, "name":"力战破虏", "selfAni_Back":"Effect/SkillEffect/10038_Charge", "selfAni_Front":"Effect/SkillEffect/10038_Charge", "selfAniTime":2.4, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"Effect/SkillEffect/10038_target_back", "targetAni_Front":"Effect/SkillEffect/10038_target_front", "targetAniTime":1.5, "targetDelay":1.6, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20038, "name":"虎啸千钧", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10039_charge", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10039_charge", "selfAniTime":1.5, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10039_target_back", "targetAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10039_target_front", "targetAniTime":0.8, "targetDelay":1.4, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10039_hit", "hitAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10039_hit", "hitAniTime":0.8, "hitDelay":1.6, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20039, "name":"风流绝世", "selfAni_Back":"Effect/SkillEffect/10040_Charge", "selfAni_Front":"Effect/SkillEffect/10040_Charge", "selfAniTime":2.6, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":1.2, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"Effect/SkillEffect/10040_hit", "hitAni_Front":"Effect/SkillEffect/10040_hit", "hitAniTime":1.5, "hitDelay":1.66, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20040, "name":"以逸待劳", "selfAni_Back":"WarEffect/9007_100_back", "selfAni_Front":"WarEffect/9007_100_front", "selfAniTime":0, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"WarEffect/9007_back", "targetAni_Front":"WarEffect/9007_front", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":0, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20041, "name":"幽影暗箭", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10042_Charge_back", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10042_Charge_front", "selfAniTime":3, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":0, "flyAni":"FX/skillEffect/10042_fly", "flyType":3, "flySpd":24, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":1.4, "hitAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10042_hit", "hitAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10042_hit", "hitAniTime":0.8, "hitDelay":1.5, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20042, "name":"噬灵之戟", "selfAni_Back":"", "selfAni_Front":"", "selfAniTime":0, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":0, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20043, "name":"战魂双戟", "selfAni_Back":"Effect/SkillEffect/10044_charge", "selfAni_Front":"Effect/SkillEffect/10044_charge", "selfAniTime":2.5, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"Effect/SkillEffect/10044_target", "targetAni_Front":"Effect/SkillEffect/10044_target", "targetAniTime":2, "targetDelay":1.6, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20044, "name":"据守千军", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10045_charge", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10045_charge", "selfAniTime":2.5, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10045_target", "targetAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10045_target", "targetAniTime":2, "targetDelay":1.6, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20045, "name":"不死之躯", "selfAni_Back":"Effect/SkillEffect/10046_Charge", "selfAni_Front":"Effect/SkillEffect/10046_Charge", "selfAniTime":3.5, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":0, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20046, "name":"苦痛血刃", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10047_charge_back", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10047_charge_front", "selfAniTime":1.9, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10047_target_back", "targetAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10047_target_front", "targetAniTime":3, "targetDelay":1.6, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10047_hit", "hitAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10047_hit", "hitAniTime":1.6, "hitDelay":3, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20047, "name":"贞烈毒刃", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10048_charge_back", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10048_charge_front", "selfAniTime":1.8, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10048_target", "targetAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10048_target", "targetAniTime":2, "targetDelay":1.5, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10048_hit", "hitAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10048_hit", "hitAniTime":2, "hitDelay":1.5, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20048, "name":"", "selfAni_Back":"WarEffect/9003_100", "selfAni_Front":"WarEffect/9003_100", "selfAniTime":0, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"WarEffect/9003", "targetAni_Front":"WarEffect/9003", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":1.7, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20049, "name":"", "selfAni_Back":"WarEffect/9017_100_back", "selfAni_Front":"WarEffect/9017_100_front", "selfAniTime":0, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"WarEffect/9017_front", "targetAni_Front":"WarEffect/9017_back", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":1.1, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20050, "name":"风卷残云", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10051_Charge", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10051_Charge", "selfAniTime":3, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10051_target_back", "targetAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10051_target_front", "targetAniTime":1.5, "targetDelay":1.7, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10051_hit", "hitAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10051_hit", "hitAniTime":1, "hitDelay":1.8, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20051, "name":"致命投掷", "selfAni_Back":"WarEffect/9055_100_back", "selfAni_Front":"WarEffect/9055_100_front", "selfAniTime":0, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"WarEffect/9055_back", "targetAni_Front":"WarEffect/9055_front", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":1.3, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20052, "name":"坚壁清野", "selfAni_Back":"Effect/SkillEffect/10053_Charge", "selfAni_Front":"Effect/SkillEffect/10053_Charge", "selfAniTime":3.5, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"WarEffect/9018_back", "targetAni_Front":"WarEffect/9018_front", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":1.7, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20053, "name":"箭无虚发", "selfAni_Back":"Effect/SkillEffect/10054_Charge_back", "selfAni_Front":"Effect/SkillEffect/10054_Charge_front", "selfAniTime":2.1, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"Effect/SkillEffect/10054_target_back", "targetAni_Front":"Effect/SkillEffect/10054_target_front", "targetAniTime":1.5, "targetDelay":2, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20054, "name":"长虹贯日", "selfAni_Back":"", "selfAni_Front":"", "selfAniTime":0, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"WarEffect/9020_front", "targetAni_Front":"WarEffect/9020_back", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":0, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20055, "name":"自然馈赠", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10056_charge", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10056_charge", "selfAniTime":2.5, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":0, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10056_hit", "hitAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10056_hit", "hitAniTime":1.4, "hitDelay":2, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20056, "name":"辕门射戟", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10057_charge_back", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10057_charge_front", "selfAniTime":2.5, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":0, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10057_hit", "hitAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10057_hit", "hitAniTime":1.5, "hitDelay":1.6, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20057, "name":"炼狱火刑", "selfAni_Back":"", "selfAni_Front":"", "selfAniTime":0, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":0, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20058, "name":"湮灭雷劫", "selfAni_Back":"", "selfAni_Front":"", "selfAniTime":0, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":0, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20059, "name":"天生傲骨", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10060_charge_back", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10060_charge_front", "selfAniTime":1.6, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":0, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10060_hit", "hitAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10060_hit", "hitAniTime":1.4, "hitDelay":2, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20060, "name":"仙途道法", "selfAni_Back":"", "selfAni_Front":"", "selfAniTime":0, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":0, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20061, "name":"医道圣手", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10062_Charge", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10062_Charge", "selfAniTime":2.3, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10062_target", "targetAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10062_target", "targetAniTime":2, "targetDelay":2, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20062, "name":"先祖呼唤", "selfAni_Back":"Effect/SkillEffect/10063_Charge", "selfAni_Front":"Effect/SkillEffect/10063_Charge", "selfAniTime":2.5, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"Effect/SkillEffect/10063_target", "targetAni_Front":"Effect/SkillEffect/10063_target", "targetAniTime":1.6, "targetDelay":1.4, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20063, "name":"堕天一击", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10064_Charge_back", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10064_Charge_front", "selfAniTime":1.2, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":0, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10064_hit", "hitAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10064_hit", "hitAniTime":1.5, "hitDelay":1.4, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20064, "name":"西凉圣女", "selfAni_Back":"", "selfAni_Front":"", "selfAniTime":0, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":0, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20065, "name":"超越之力", "selfAni_Back":"", "selfAni_Front":"", "selfAniTime":0, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":0, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20066, "name":"威震山河", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10067_Charge", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10067_Charge", "selfAniTime":0.9, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10067_target", "targetAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10067_target", "targetAniTime":2.5, "targetDelay":1.5, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20067, "name":"神鬼诛杀", "selfAni_Back":"", "selfAni_Front":"", "selfAniTime":0, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":0, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20068, "name":"卧龙遗策", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10069_Charge", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10069_Charge", "selfAniTime":1.5, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":0, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/10069_hit", "hitAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/10069_hit", "hitAniTime":2.7, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20069, "name":"七步成诗", "selfAni_Back":"Effect/SkillEffect/10070_Charge_back", "selfAni_Front":"Effect/SkillEffect/10070_Charge_front", "selfAniTime":2, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"Effect/SkillEffect/10070_target", "targetAni_Front":"Effect/SkillEffect/10070_target", "targetAniTime":1.5, "targetDelay":1.53, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20070, "name":"陷阵强盾", "selfAni_Back":"Effect/SkillEffect/10071_Charge_back", "selfAni_Front":"Effect/SkillEffect/10071_Charge_front", "selfAniTime":2.5, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"Effect/SkillEffect/10071_target", "targetAni_Front":"Effect/SkillEffect/10071_target", "targetAniTime":1.6, "targetDelay":1.35, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20071, "name":"", "selfAni_Back":"", "selfAni_Front":"", "selfAniTime":0, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":0, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20072, "name":"", "selfAni_Back":"", "selfAni_Front":"", "selfAniTime":0, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":0, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20073, "name":"", "selfAni_Back":"", "selfAni_Front":"", "selfAniTime":0, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":0, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20074, "name":"", "selfAni_Back":"", "selfAni_Front":"", "selfAniTime":0, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":0, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20075, "name":"", "selfAni_Back":"Effect/SkillEffect/10076_Charge", "selfAni_Front":"Effect/SkillEffect/10076_Charge", "selfAniTime":2.5, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"Effect/SkillEffect/10076_target", "targetAni_Front":"Effect/SkillEffect/10076_target", "targetAniTime":1.6, "targetDelay":1.4, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20076, "name":"", "selfAni_Back":"", "selfAni_Front":"", "selfAniTime":0, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":0, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20077, "name":"", "selfAni_Back":"", "selfAni_Front":"", "selfAniTime":0, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":0, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":20078, "name":"", "selfAni_Back":"", "selfAni_Front":"", "selfAniTime":0, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":0, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":30000, "name":"疯魔烈焰", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/19001_Charge", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/19001_Charge", "selfAniTime":5, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/19001_target", "targetAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/19001_target", "targetAniTime":3.5, "targetDelay":1.8, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":30001, "name":"鬼神乱舞", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/19002_Charge", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/19002_Charge", "selfAniTime":1.5, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/19002_target", "targetAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/19002_target", "targetAniTime":3, "targetDelay":1.3, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":30002, "name":"黄天神雷", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/19003_Charge", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/19003_Charge", "selfAniTime":2.5, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/19003_target", "targetAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/19003_target", "targetAniTime":3, "targetDelay":1.5, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":80001, "name":"八方烬灭", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/UI_zhugong", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/UI_zhugong", "selfAniTime":1.2, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/93001_target_back", "targetAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/93001_target_front", "targetAniTime":2.5, "targetDelay":1, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":80002, "name":"蓬莱仙莲", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/UI_zhugong", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/UI_zhugong", "selfAniTime":1.2, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/93002_target", "targetAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/93002_target", "targetAniTime":1.7, "targetDelay":1, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":80003, "name":"坚毅风采", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/UI_zhugong", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/UI_zhugong", "selfAniTime":1.2, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/93003_target", "targetAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/93003_target", "targetAniTime":1.7, "targetDelay":1, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":80004, "name":"勇气战歌", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/UI_zhugong", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/UI_zhugong", "selfAniTime":1.2, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/93004_target", "targetAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/93004_target", "targetAniTime":2.5, "targetDelay":1, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":80005, "name":"风雷结阵", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/UI_zhugong", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/UI_zhugong", "selfAniTime":1.2, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/93005_target", "targetAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/93005_target", "targetAniTime":2.7, "targetDelay":1, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":80006, "name":"驱夜断愁", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/UI_zhugong", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/UI_zhugong", "selfAniTime":1.2, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/93006_target", "targetAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/93006_target", "targetAniTime":7, "targetDelay":1, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":80007, "name":"兵贵神速", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/UI_zhugong", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/UI_zhugong", "selfAniTime":1.2, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":1, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":80008, "name":"清风垂露", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/UI_zhugong", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/UI_zhugong", "selfAniTime":1.2, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":1, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":80009, "name":"七星续命", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/UI_zhugong", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/UI_zhugong", "selfAniTime":1.2, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":1, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":80010, "name":"南蛮蛊术", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/UI_zhugong", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/UI_zhugong", "selfAniTime":1.2, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":1, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":80011, "name":"妙舞神扬", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/UI_zhugong", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/UI_zhugong", "selfAniTime":1.2, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":1, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":80012, "name":"嗜血狂暴", "selfAni_Back":"FX/skillEffect/UI_zhugong", "selfAni_Front":"FX/skillEffect/UI_zhugong", "selfAniTime":1.2, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":1, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":100000, "name":"投石兵", "selfAni_Back":"", "selfAni_Front":"", "selfAniTime":0, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"WarEffect/91003_200_target_back", "targetAni_Front":"WarEffect/91003_200_target_front", "targetAniTime":1.5, "targetDelay":0.6, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":100001, "name":"炮车", "selfAni_Back":"", "selfAni_Front":"", "selfAniTime":0, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"WarEffect/91002_200_target_back", "targetAni_Front":"WarEffect/91002_200_target_front", "targetAniTime":1.5, "targetDelay":0.6, "flyAni":"", "flyType":0, "flySpd":0, "flyDirection":0, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0, "hitAni_Back":"", "hitAni_Front":"", "hitAniTime":0, "hitDelay":0, "hitCycle":0 },
{ "ID":100002, "name":"月弩车", "selfAni_Back":"", "selfAni_Front":"", "selfAniTime":0, "selfDelay":0, "targetAni_Back":"", "targetAni_Front":"", "targetAniTime":0, "targetDelay":0, "flyAni":"WarEffect/91001_300", "flyType":3, "flySpd":5, "flyDirection":1, "flyPathWayType":0, "flyDelay":0.5, "hitAni_Back":"WarEffect/91001_200", "hitAni_Front":"WarEffect/91001_200", "hitAniTime":0.8, "hitDelay":0.7, "hitCycle":0 }]